Common diseases
The following,
are comments on various diseases
contained in the MEDLINEPLUS website.
Tonsillitis is an inflammation
of one or both tonsils, located on the
lateral wall of the oropharynx,
its most common cause is a viral infection,
since many viruses attack the respiratory
tract and affect the tonsils, that
are part of the body’s immune system.
Asthma It is caused by swelling and contraction
of the muscles around the airways,
which makes breathing
difficult. Some of your symptoms are
chest tightness or shortness of breath.
Bronchitis is inflammation of the lower
airway caused by inflammation of
the respiratory tract due to viral
infections, such as colds or influenza.
Some of your tests are sputum
test or chest x-ray.
Regarding its symptoms it can cause cough,
fatigue and usually low fever.
For more information, please consult
the MEDLINEPLUS website.